



# **Bailey Mazur**

Columbus, Ohio 614-373-2182 bmmazur183@gmail.com

I am a UX designer with a background in art and game design.

My passion lies in building engaging interactive experiences.

My strength lies in my constantly evolving skill set and my ability to adapt to new challenges.

# **Work Experience**



#### Intern

05/2018 to 08/2018

Columbus Creative Design

Columbus, Ohio

My summer internship at Columbus Creative Design had me carefully editing up to 200 interior and exterior photos a day, crafting detailed presentations of properties through video editing, and constructing professional websites using client approved photos and videos.

## **Image Annotator**

05/2020 to 09/2020

Zen3 Tech Infosolutions

Remote

As an image annotator for Zen3 my job was to apply creative solutions to expedite the image annotation process, allowing me to process up to 200 frames a day.

# **Skills**



2D Art - 6 years

3D Art - 3 years

Unity - 3 years

### **Education**



#### **Cleveland Institute of Art**

Bachelor's Game Design Cleveland, Ohio

08/2015 to 05/2019